<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Jason White</title>
    <link>//jasonwhite.us/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Jason White</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 21:03:15 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//jasonwhite.us/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Uses</title>
      <link>//jasonwhite.us/uses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 19:29:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//jasonwhite.us/uses/</guid>
      <description>I love reading other peoples &amp;lsquo;Uses&amp;rsquo; pages so I thought I&amp;rsquo;d make my own. It feels weird to write your own and I&amp;rsquo;m not entirely sure what to write, but here we are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>//jasonwhite.us/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 22:30:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//jasonwhite.us/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me My name is Jason. Professionally I&amp;rsquo;m a web designer and developer, but outside of work I really enjoy photographing things. I live in Charlotte, North Carolina with my husband. Dog is pending.
In 2020 I decided I wanted to be a little more hands-on. I enjoyed the days when everyone had a website and shared little snippets of their personal life or hobbies. Before services and web applications became the norm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archives</title>
      <link>//jasonwhite.us/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 22:57:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//jasonwhite.us/archives/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Riverbanks Zoo</title>
      <link>//jasonwhite.us/journal/riverbanks-zoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 21:03:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//jasonwhite.us/journal/riverbanks-zoo/</guid>
      <description>For our buddy Chris&#39; birthday this year, he wanted to go to the Riverbanks Zoo. I love zoos. I will always be down to go to a zoo. This zoo in particular is cute. It isn&amp;rsquo;t very big but that turned out to be a good thing. Walking around doesn&amp;rsquo;t take most of the day, so you can actually spend time checking out the animals. And you get to see them up close!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biltmore Birthday</title>
      <link>//jasonwhite.us/journal/biltmore-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 18:35:44 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//jasonwhite.us/journal/biltmore-birthday/</guid>
      <description>For my bithday this year, Mitch surprised me with a trip to Biltmore. I&amp;rsquo;ve lived in North Carolina my whole life but I&amp;rsquo;ve never been. And now I want to go back any time I get the chance! It is breathtaking. The shear beauty of the place is so overwhelming I don&amp;rsquo;t even really know how to describe it. It&amp;rsquo;s straight-up out of a fairy tale.
 90mm Tele-Elmarit / Kodak Portra 800</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating Matt and Allen</title>
      <link>//jasonwhite.us/journal/matt-allen-engagement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 22:18:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//jasonwhite.us/journal/matt-allen-engagement/</guid>
      <description>Allen (middle) and Matt (right) are getting hitched! Couldn&amp;rsquo;t be happier for these two!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camera Scanning</title>
      <link>//jasonwhite.us/journal/camera-scanning/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 22:19:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//jasonwhite.us/journal/camera-scanning/</guid>
      <description>Why Use a Digital Camera for Scanning? This is a subject I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting to write about for a while now. One of my first ideas for a post, really. My scanning setup has changed so much since I first started &amp;ldquo;scanning&amp;rdquo; with a digital camera. I finally realized that it&amp;rsquo;s going to keep changing and I should just write about the damn thing, already. This is a long one, but hopefully informative to people that are interested in making digital copies of their film negatives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April Book Pickups</title>
      <link>//jasonwhite.us/journal/april-book-pickups-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 22:53:18 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//jasonwhite.us/journal/april-book-pickups-2021/</guid>
      <description>Didn&amp;rsquo;t mean for this to be a series, but a few books came in this month. Following Steidl is a double-edged sword. On one hand, I may go broke. On the other hand, I get to find out about new releases. And boy do they publish some beautiful books. Our Town by Michael von Graffenried is no exception. This book piqued my interest because it was shot in New Bern, North Carolina and I&amp;rsquo;m from eastern NC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring in the South</title>
      <link>//jasonwhite.us/journal/spring-in-the-south/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 08:59:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//jasonwhite.us/journal/spring-in-the-south/</guid>
      <description>Spring has certainly sprung here in the south. All three of the photos in this post are from different areas of North Carolina. Charlotte, Jacksonville and Raleigh. I wish I had a more pleasant reason for traveling all over the state this month, but the truth is, April was a tough one. I lost four people in my life. Losing someone is never easy. Losing multiple people within days apart from each other is especially hard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March Book Pickups</title>
      <link>//jasonwhite.us/journal/march-book-pickups/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 20:37:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//jasonwhite.us/journal/march-book-pickups/</guid>
      <description>Picked up a few books this month. A few of these I&amp;rsquo;ve wanted for many years. The Jim Marshall book I&amp;rsquo;d only heard of recently. There&amp;rsquo;s also a documentary of the same title , but I believe due to Covid the release date was pushed back to sometime this year.
The Vivian Maier book on her street photography is a stunner. Every single photograph is incredible. Her story is incredible. If you&amp;rsquo;ve never heard of her I highly recommend watching Finding Vivian Maier .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banana Pudding and a New Lens</title>
      <link>//jasonwhite.us/journal/banana-pudding-and-a-new-lens/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 20:11:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//jasonwhite.us/journal/banana-pudding-and-a-new-lens/</guid>
      <description>Mitch made banana pudding for Super Bowl LV from a friend of a friends recipe, I believe. It was delicious. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if banana pudding is a thing outside of the south eastern United States, but you should try it sometime if not. Those Nilla Wafers, though.
Normally I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t just sit around snapping photos of Mitch cooking, as cute as he is. But I had a new lens to test out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photowalk With New Friends</title>
      <link>//jasonwhite.us/journal/photowalk-with-new-friends/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 21:30:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//jasonwhite.us/journal/photowalk-with-new-friends/</guid>
      <description>Jesse and I have been trying to meetup for months to go on a photowalk. Finally the stars aligned, and so did good weather on a Saturday. A few more people in his photo group showed up and we took off around the neighborhood to make some photos. It&amp;rsquo;s always nice to get out and shoot, and meeting new people while doing it is a huge bonus. And I can&amp;rsquo;t forget Otis, the most goodest boy, a golden retriever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last Day of 2020</title>
      <link>//jasonwhite.us/journal/last-day-of-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 20:32:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//jasonwhite.us/journal/last-day-of-2020/</guid>
      <description>The last day of 2020, here at least, was covered in a dense fog for most of the day. I kept eyeing it out the window thinking McAlpine Creek Park would be really fun to make photographs at right now. It didn&amp;rsquo;t look like it was going away so I packed my gear and headed out the door. I could of rode my bike but the drive is a little faster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adams School House</title>
      <link>//jasonwhite.us/journal/adams-school-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2020 19:45:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//jasonwhite.us/journal/adams-school-house/</guid>
      <description>On Christmas day after having dinner at my aunt&amp;rsquo;s house and watching the kids open their gifts, I ventured around my hometown a little bit to take photos. One location I definitely wanted to photograph is the old Adams School House. It&amp;rsquo;s right up the road from the house I grew up in. I actually meant to photograph it early in the morning so that the sun would be in front rather than behind, but overall I like how this turned out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas 2020</title>
      <link>//jasonwhite.us/journal/christmas-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 05:42:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//jasonwhite.us/journal/christmas-2020/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s safe to say that 2020 has been a shit year for most, if not everyone. The timeline a seemingly never-ending rollercoaster of ups and downs, and downs&amp;hellip;and downs. So not really a rollercoaster at all. More like one of those rides that just drop you.
The photo above was taken during a CLT Shooters photo walk in mid-town. These are fun, laid back photo walks with local photographers. Models come along as well for people to practice portraits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>McAlpine Creek Park</title>
      <link>//jasonwhite.us/journal/mcalpine-creek-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2020 20:59:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//jasonwhite.us/journal/mcalpine-creek-park/</guid>
      <description>Why did I not come here during peak fall colors? Next year, I guess.
This is one of two parks by our house and during the pandemic have been a wonderful little getaway from being stuck inside. Never too crowded, but still people doing mostly the same as us. Just out for a stroll to get fresh air.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gatlinburg, TN</title>
      <link>//jasonwhite.us/journal/gatlinburg/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 21:25:40 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//jasonwhite.us/journal/gatlinburg/</guid>
      <description>We took a nice trip to Gatlinburg TN in November. The photo above was shot from one of the balconies of our cabin. It was an excellent, refreshing trip. I haven&amp;rsquo;t developed or scanned all of the photos just yet, but I will update this post with some shots from Clingman&amp;rsquo;s Dome when I do. I can&amp;rsquo;t properly scan 120 film at this time. I ordered an Essential Film Holder but it seems to have been lost in the mail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bald Head Island</title>
      <link>//jasonwhite.us/journal/bald-head-island/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 23:36:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//jasonwhite.us/journal/bald-head-island/</guid>
      <description>A trip to Bald Head Island during vacation was one of my favorite days. Although hot, the weather was sunny and clear. Lots of spectacular houses thoughout the whole island, and the transportation method is pretty much golf cart only.
 Kodak Portra 160
  More photos can be viewed here. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunset Beach</title>
      <link>//jasonwhite.us/journal/sunset-beach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 22:31:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//jasonwhite.us/journal/sunset-beach/</guid>
      <description>A much needed trip away from everything during all of the chaos that is 2020. They named it Sunset Beach but I feel like it should have been named Sunrise Beach. Unfortunately I only got up for one sunrise, and it was definitely worth it.
More photos can be viewed here. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Made a Camera Strap</title>
      <link>//jasonwhite.us/journal/i-made-a-camera-strap/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 08:13:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//jasonwhite.us/journal/i-made-a-camera-strap/</guid>
      <description>I had a photo walk scheduled this past weekend with a couple local photographers but the weather had other plans. I was pretty bummed, but I&amp;rsquo;ve had the idea of making a camera strap for a while. A week prior I had already ordered a couple Horween CXL leather strips but I needed a few other things. So off to Tandy Leather we go! Went. We went, past tense.
Having a local Tandy is handy (heh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pressure Washing</title>
      <link>//jasonwhite.us/journal/pressure-washing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 23:00:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//jasonwhite.us/journal/pressure-washing/</guid>
      <description>We bought a pressure washer the other day. Well, a few weeks ago at this point. I&amp;rsquo;ve been pretty slow to get to film development lately.
Anywho, pressure washers are amazing. Like, amazing. I honestly didn&amp;rsquo;t think our driveway was so dirty. Boy was I wrong. You can see a difference at the end of the driveway.
 Ilford HP5 pushed to 1600
  The patio makes me proud to look at.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Lives Matter Mural</title>
      <link>//jasonwhite.us/journal/black-lives-matter-mural/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 13:22:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//jasonwhite.us/journal/black-lives-matter-mural/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday, June 9, multiple local artists were commissioned by the city of Charlotte to create a large mural that read &amp;ldquo;BLACK LIVES MATTER&amp;rdquo; between 3rd and 4th streets on S. Tryon. Each artist or team of artists took a letter and went to work. The entire mural was finished in a day and from what I&amp;rsquo;ve read they had little time to prepare. The result is quite amazing. Each letter very different reflecting each artist or artists&#39; styles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quarantine Days III</title>
      <link>//jasonwhite.us/journal/quarantine-days-iii/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 13:22:40 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//jasonwhite.us/journal/quarantine-days-iii/</guid>
      <description>Tomorrow they&amp;rsquo;re going to start &amp;ldquo;Phase II&amp;rdquo; of reopening around these parts. This means restaurants, bars, gyms and salons can open at limited capacity. I&amp;rsquo;m still pretty content staying at home but I do hope we get to have socially distanced friend meetups sometime soon.
 Ilford HP5 pushed to 1600
  Things have been the pretty much the same at home. Walks around the neighborhood park and bike rides with a couple friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quarantine Days II</title>
      <link>//jasonwhite.us/journal/quarantine-days-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 21:19:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//jasonwhite.us/journal/quarantine-days-ii/</guid>
      <description>Learned from friends today that the stay at home order in North Carolina is being extended until May 8th. Reopening will happen in three phases with the possibility to go backwards. The curve is &amp;ldquo;flattening&amp;rdquo; around Charlotte according to data a kind redditor keeps posting in /r/charlotte.
 Kodak Portra 400
  The weather has been mostly beautiful so it&amp;rsquo;s hard not to go for walks after work. There are many trails in our neighboring park to keep it fresh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quarantine Days I</title>
      <link>//jasonwhite.us/journal/quartine-days-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 14:31:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//jasonwhite.us/journal/quartine-days-i/</guid>
      <description>Like most others, we&amp;rsquo;ve been laying low. Only trips to the grocery store or Costco for essential items. Haven&amp;rsquo;t seen any friends in person for weeks. Our only real way to get out and about is to walk in the park by our neighborhood. It helps.
 iPhone 11 Pro
  I try to focus on any positives there may be during all of this. I&amp;rsquo;m fortunate to have a quarantine buddy and a job that allows me to work from home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dog Sitting</title>
      <link>//jasonwhite.us/journal/dog-sitting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 20:46:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//jasonwhite.us/journal/dog-sitting/</guid>
      <description>Got to watch Farley and Memphis for the day while Robbie and Ryan had some house work being done. They&amp;rsquo;re about as low-maintenance as it gets.
We&amp;rsquo;ve talked about getting a dog for a while now. The idea needs to stay on hold for a bit longer until we get some house things finished. Although, with all the work from home days lately, this might be the best time to raise a puppy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deadmau5</title>
      <link>//jasonwhite.us/journal/deadmau5-in-dc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//jasonwhite.us/journal/deadmau5-in-dc/</guid>
      <description>Much earlier this year my friend Ryan asked us if we&amp;rsquo;d like to drive up to DC and see Deadmau5 around Thanksgiving.
I didn&amp;rsquo;t know what to think at first as far as seeing Deadmau5 live, goes. But a trip to DC always sounds like a good time.
There ended up being eight of us and we decided to rent a shuttle van to make the trip up, which everyone agrees was a fantastic idea.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
